[
  {
    "prompt": "science",
    "answer": "ғылым",
    "level": "B1"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "technology",
    "answer": "технология",
    "level": "B1"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "data",
    "answer": "дерек",
    "level": "B1"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "information",
    "answer": "ақпарат",
    "level": "B1"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "analysis",
    "answer": "талдау",
    "level": "B1"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "result",
    "answer": "нәтиже",
    "level": "B1"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "method",
    "answer": "әдіс",
    "level": "B1"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "model",
    "answer": "модель",
    "level": "B1"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "algorithm",
    "answer": "алгоритм",
    "level": "B1"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "problem",
    "answer": "мәселе",
    "level": "B1"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "solution",
    "answer": "шешім",
    "level": "B1"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "project",
    "answer": "жоба",
    "level": "B1"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "research",
    "answer": "зерттеу",
    "level": "B1"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "experiment",
    "answer": "тәжірибе",
    "level": "B1"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "presentation",
    "answer": "презентация",
    "level": "B1"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "report",
    "answer": "есеп",
    "level": "B1"
  }
]